Guide to the Jewish Labor Committee Records, Part II WAG.025.002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Administrative and Organizational Records
  - Subseries I:F: Women's Division Records, 1947-1956
    - Women's Division: Correspondence, Jan 1949-Apr 1949 (Box 67, Folder 45)
    - Women's Division: Correspondence, May 1949-Sep 1949 (Box 67, Folder 46)
    - Women's Division: Correspondence, Oct 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 67, Folder 47)
    - Women's Division: Correspondence, Jan 1950-Sep 1950 (Box 67, Folder 48)
    - Women's Division: Correspondence, Oct 1950-Dec 1950 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      Microfilm reel#: 204
    - Women's Division: Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Women's Division: Correspondence, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Women's Division: Correspondence, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Women's Division: Correspondence, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Women's Division: Correspondence, Jan 1956-Sep 1956 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Women's Division: Correspondence, Oct 1956-Dec 1956 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Conferences/Meetings, 1948 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Conferences/Meetings, 1949 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Conferences/Meetings, 1950 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Conferences/Meetings, 1951 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Conferences/Meetings, 1952 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Conferences/Meetings, 1953 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Conferences/Meetings, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      Microfilm reel#: 205
    - Conferences/Meetings, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Chapters: General, 1949-1956 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Boston, MA, 1953-1956 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Chicago, IL, 1949-1954 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Chicago, IL, 1955-1956 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Cincinnati, Ohio, 1948-1949 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Cleveland, Ohio, 1951-1956 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Cloak Joint Board, 1948-1951 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Cloak Joint Board, 1952-1956 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Detroit, MI, 1951-1956 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Kansas City, MO, 1951-1956 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Local 22, 1947-1956 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Los Angeles, 1949-1956 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Manhattan Chapter, 1953-1956 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Mendelson, S., 1948-1956 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Minneapolis, MN, 1950 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Montreal, 1949-1956 (Box 68, Folder 31)
      Microfilm reel#: 206
    - North Bronx, NY, 1949-1950 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Pittsburgh, PA, 1949-1956 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - Professional Women's Chapter, 1955 (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - Progressive Women's Club, 1949-1953 (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - Queens Village, NY, 1950-1956 (Box 68, Folder 36)
    - San Francisco, CA, 1956 (Box 68, Folder 37)
    - Toronto, 1949-1955 (Box 68, Folder 38)
    - Washington D.C., 1954-1956 (Box 68, Folder 39)
    - West Bronx, NY, 1948-1956 (Box 68, Folder 40)
    - Women's Club Branch 637, 1954 (Box 68, Folder 41)
    - Publicity, 1947-1956 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Women's Division: Bulletins, 1949-1956 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Subseries I:G: Workmen's Circle Division Records, 1945-1956
    - Workmen's Circle Division: Minutes, 1945 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jan 1945 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Feb 1945 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Mar 1945 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Apr 1945 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, May 1945 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      Microfilm reel#: 207
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jun 1945 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jul 1945-Aug 1945 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Sep 1945-Oct 1945 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Nov 1945 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Dec 1945 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jan 1946 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Feb 1946 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Mar 1946 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Apr 1946 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, May 1946 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jun 1946 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jul 1946 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Aug 1946-Sep 1946 (Box 69, Folder 21)
      Microfilm reel#: 208
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Oct 1946 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Nov 1946 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Dec 1946 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jan 1947-Feb 1947 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Mar 1947 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Apr 1947 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, May 1947 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jun 1947 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jul 1947-Aug 1947 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Sep 1947-Oct 1947 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Nov 1947 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      Microfilm reel#: 209
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Dec 1947 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jan 1948 (Box 70, Folder 9)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Feb 1948 (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Mar 1948 (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Apr 1948 (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, May 1948 (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jun 1948-Jul 1948 (Box 70, Folder 14)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Aug 1948-Sep 1948 (Box 70, Folder 15)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Oct 1948 (Box 70, Folder 16)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Nov 1948 (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Dec 1948 (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jan 1949-Feb 1949 (Box 70, Folder 19)
      Microfilm reel#: 210
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Mar 1949 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Apr 1949 (Box 70, Folder 21)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, May 1949 (Box 70, Folder 22)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jun 1949-Aug 1949 (Box 70, Folder 23)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Sep 1949-Oct 1949 (Box 70, Folder 24)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Nov 1949 (Box 70, Folder 25)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Dec 1949 (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jan 1950 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Feb 1950 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Mar 1950 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Apr 1950 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, May 1950 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jun 1950 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      Microfilm reel#: 211
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jul 1950-Aug 1950 (Box 71, Folder 8)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Sep 1950 (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Oct 1950 (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Nov 1950 (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Dec 1950 (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jan 1951 (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Feb 1951 (Box 71, Folder 14)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Mar 1951 (Box 71, Folder 15)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Apr 1951 (Box 71, Folder 16)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, May 1951 (Box 71, Folder 17)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jun 1951 (Box 71, Folder 18)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jul 1951-Aug 1951 (Box 71, Folder 19)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Sep 1951 (Box 71, Folder 20)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Oct 1951 (Box 71, Folder 21)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Nov 1951 (Box 71, Folder 22)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Dec 1951 (Box 71, Folder 23)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jan 1952-Feb 1952 (Box 71, Folder 24)
      Microfilm reel#: 212
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Mar 1952-Aug 1952 (Box 71, Folder 25)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Sep 1952-Dec 1952 (Box 71, Folder 26)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jan 1953-May 1953 (Box 71, Folder 27)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jun 1953-Oct 1953 (Box 71, Folder 28)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Nov 1953-Dec 1953 (Box 71, Folder 29)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jan 1954-May 1954 (Box 71, Folder 30)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jun 1954-Oct 1954 (Box 71, Folder 31)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Nov 1954-Dec 1954 (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Jan 1955-Mar 1955 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Apr 1955-Jul 1955 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Workmen's Circle Division, Aug 1955-Dec 1955 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      Microfilm reel#: 213
    - Workmen's Circle Division, 1956 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Workmen's Circle Schools, 1945-1948 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Workmen's Circle Schools, 1949-1950 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Workmen's Circle Schools, 1951-1956 (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Scrapbook, Jan 1948-Dec 1954 (Reel 214)
    - Scrapbook, Feb 1948-Dec 1951 (Reel 214)
    - Scrapbook, Feb 1948-Jul 1948 (Reel 214)
    - Scrapbook, Aug 1948-Dec 1948 (Reel 215)
    - Scrapbook, Mar 1949-Aug 1949 (Reel 215)
    - Scrapbook, Mar 1949-Jan 1950 (Reel 215)
    - Scrapbook, Jan 1950-Apr 1950 (Reel 215)
    - Scrapbook, Jan 1951-May 1951 (Reel 216)
    - Scrapbook, Jan 1952-Jun 1952 (Reel 216)
    - Scrapbook, Jan 1952-Dec 1952 (Reel 216)
    - Scrapbook, Jan 1953-Jun 1953 (Reel 217)
    - Scrapbook, Jan 1953-Dec 1953 (Reel 217)
    - Scrapbook, Jul 1953-Nov 1953 (Reel 217)
    - Scrapbook, Jan 1954-Dec 1954 (Reel 217)
    - Scrapbook, Jan 1955-Dec 1955 (Reel 218)
    - Scrapbook, Jan 1956-Dec 1956 (Reel 218)
    - Scrapbook, Jun 1956-Dec 1956 (Reel 218)
- Series II: American Cities
  - American Cities-- General, 1949-1953 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    Microfilm reel#: 218
  - Alabama --General, Jun 1948-Aug 1956 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Birmingham, AL, Mar 1948-Dec 1956 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - Arizona: General, Jan 1951-Dec 1956 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - California: General, Mar 1948-Dec 1956 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - Fresno, CA, 1950-1952 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1948-Mar 1948 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Apr 1948-Jun 1948 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jul 1948-Oct 1948 (Box 73, Folder 9)
    Microfilm reel#: 219
  - Los Angeles, CA, Nov 1948-Dec 1948 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1949-Apr 1949 (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - Los Angeles, CA, May 1949-Aug 1949 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Sep 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1950-Apr 1950 (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Los Angeles, CA, May 1950-Aug 1950 (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Sep 1950-Dec 1950 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1951-Mar 1951 (Box 73, Folder 17)
    Microfilm reel#: 220
  - Los Angeles, CA, Apr 1951-Jun 1951 (Box 73, Folder 18)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jun 1951-Oct 1951 (Box 73, Folder 19)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Nov 1951-Dec 1951 (Box 73, Folder 20)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1952-May 1952 (Box 73, Folder 21)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jun 1952-Sep 1952 (Box 73, Folder 22)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Oct 1952-Dec 1952 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1953-Mar 1953 (Box 74, Folder 2)
    Microfilm reel#: 221
  - Los Angeles, CA, Apr 1953-Jun 1953 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jul 1953-Oct 1953 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Nov 1953-Dec 1953 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1954-Feb 1954 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Mar 1954-May 1954 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jun 1954-Sep 1954 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Oct 1954-Dec 1954 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - Los Angeles, CA, 1955, undated (Box 74, Folder 10)
    Microfilm reel#: 222
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1955-Feb 1955 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Mar 1955-Apr 1955 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - Los Angeles, CA, May 1955-Aug 1955 (Box 74, Folder 13)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Sep 1955-Dec 1955 (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Jan 1956-Apr 1956 (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Los Angeles, CA, May 1956-Aug 1956 (Box 74, Folder 16)
  - Los Angeles, CA, Sep 1956-Dec 1956 (Box 74, Folder 17)
  - Petaluma, CA, 1951 (Box 74, Folder 18)
  - Oakland, CA, Jul 1948-Sep 1956 (Box 74, Folder 19)
  - San Diego, CA, 1949-1953 (Box 74, Folder 20)
  - San Francisco, CA, 1948-1956 (Box 74, Folder 21)
  - Stockton, CA, 1948-1951 (Box 74, Folder 22)
  - Colorado: General, 1948 (Box 74, Folder 23)
    Microfilm reel#: 223
  - Denver, CO, 1948-1950 (Box 74, Folder 24)
  - Connecticut: General, 1948-1955 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Ansonia, CT, 1948-1953 (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Bridgeport, CT, 1948-1955 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  - Hartford, CT, 1949-1956 (Box 75, Folder 4)
  - New Haven, CT, 1946-1956 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - New London, CT, 1955 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Norwich, CT, 1948-1951 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Willimantic, CT, 1948-1950 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - Delaware: General, 1950 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Wilmington, DE, 1948-1955 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Florida: General, 1952-1953 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Jacksonville, FL, 1948-1951, 1954 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Miami, FL (and Miami Beach), 1948-1949 (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - Miami, FL, 1950 (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Miami, FL, 1951 (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Miami, FL, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Miami, FL, 1952-1953 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Miami, FL, 1954-1955 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Miami, FL, 1956 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Atlanta, GA, 1948-1949 (Box 75, Folder 20)
    Microfilm reel#: 224
  - Atlanta, GA, 1950-1954 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Atlanta, GA, 1955-1956 (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Savannah, GA, 1948-1956 (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Illinois: General, 1948-1952 (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1948-Jun 1948 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - Chicago, IL, Jul 1948-Dec 1948 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1949-Apr 1949 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - Chicago, IL, May 1949-Aug 1949 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Chicago, IL, Sep 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1950-Jun 1950 (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Chicago, IL, Jul 1950-Dec 1950 (Box 75, Folder 31)
    Microfilm reel#: 225
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1951-May 1951 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Chicago, IL, Jun 1951-Sep 1951 (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Chicago, IL, Oct 1951-Dec 1951 (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1952-Apr 1952 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Chicago, IL, May 1952-Jun 1952 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Chicago, IL, Jul 1952-Sep 1952 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Chicago, IL, Oct 1952-Dec 1952 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1953-Apr 1953 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Chicago, IL, Jul 1953-Aug 1953 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    Microfilm reel#: 226
  - Chicago, IL, Sep 1953-Dec 1953 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1954-Jun 1954 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Chicago, IL, Jul 1954-Dec 1954 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1955-Mar 1955 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Chicago, IL, Apr 1955-Jun 1955 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Chicago, IL, Jul 1955-Dec 1955 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Chicago, IL, Jan 1956-Jun 1956 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - Chicago, IL, Jul 1956-Dec 1956 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Indiana: General, 1949-1956 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    Microfilm reel#: 227
  - Fort Wayne, IN, 1955 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Hammond, IN, 1946-1956 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Indianapolis, IN, 1951 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - South Bend, IN, 1952-1954 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Iowa: General, 1948-1956 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Des Moines, IA, 1948-1955 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Sioux City, IA, 1949-1955 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Kentucky: General, 1948-1955 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Louisiana: General, 1951 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - New Orleans, LA, 1948-1955 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Shreveport, LA, 1949-1950 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Maine: General, 1950-1953 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Maryland: General, 1948-1954 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1948 (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1949 (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1950 (Box 76, Folder 31)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1951-1952 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1953-1954 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Baltimore, MD, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts: General, 1948-1955 (Box 77, Folder 5)
    Microfilm reel#: 228
  - Boston, MA, 1948-1949 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Boston, MA, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Boston, MA, 1952-1953 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Boston, MA, 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Boston, MA, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Brockton, MA, 1951-1955 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Chelsea, MA, 1950-1956 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Dorchester, MA, 1948-1956 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Fall River, MA, 1948-1955 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Holyoke, MA, 1949-1956 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Lawrence, MA, 1949-1955 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - Lynn, MA, 1948-1953 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - New Bedford, MA, 1948-1956 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Springfield, MA, 1948-1954 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Worcester, MA, 1948-1952 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Michigan: General, 1951-1956 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Detroit, MI, Jan 1948-Jun 1948 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Detroit, MI, Jul 1948-Dec 1948 (Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Detroit, MI, Jan 1949-May 1949 (Box 77, Folder 24)
    Microfilm reel#: 229
  - Detroit, MI, Jun 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 77, Folder 25)
  - Detroit, MI, 1950 (Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Detroit, MI, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 27)
  - Detroit, MI, 1952 (Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Detroit, MI, 1953 (Box 77, Folder 29)
  - Detroit, MI, 1954-1955 (Box 77, Folder 30)
  - Detroit, MI, 1956 (Box 77, Folder 31)
  - Grand Rapids, MI, 1948-1956 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Minnesota: General, 1949-1956 (Box 78, Folder 2)
    Microfilm reel#: 230
  - Minneapolis, MN, 1948-1956 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Duluth, MN, 1949-1956 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - St. Paul, MN, 1948-1956 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - Mississippi: General, 1954 (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - Missouri: General, 1953-1955 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - Kansas City, MO, 1948-1956 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - St. Louis, MO, 1948-1956 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Omaha, NE, 1948-1955 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - New Hampshire: General, 1949 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - New Jersey, 1949-1956 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Asbury Park, NJ, 1953-1955 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - Atlantic City, NJ, 1949-1956 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Elizabeth, NJ, 1948-1950 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Hackensack, NJ, 1951 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - Highland Park, NJ, 1948-1950 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - Hoboken, NJ, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - Jersey City, NJ, 1948-1955 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Lakewood, NJ, 1948-1951 (Box 78, Folder 20)
  - Long Branch, NJ, 1948-1953 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Morristown, NJ, 1948-1952 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - New Brunswick, NJ, 1948-1956 (Box 78, Folder 23)
  - Newark, NJ, 1948-1956 (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - Passaic, NJ, 1948-1955 (Box 78, Folder 25)
  - Paterson, NJ, 1948-1949 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - Paterson, NJ, 1950-1956 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - Perth Amboy, NJ, 1949-1953 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - Roosevelt, NJ, 1948-1954 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - Roselle, NJ, 1948-1951 (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - Trenton, NJ, 1948-1956 (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - Union City, NJ, 1948-1949 (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - New York: General, 1948-1955 (Box 78, Folder 33)
    Microfilm reel#: 231
  - Albany, NY, 1948-1956 (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - Bronx, NY, 1948-1956 (Box 78, Folder 35)
  - Brooklyn, NY, 1948-1951 (Box 78, Folder 36)
  - Brooklyn, NY, Jan 1952-May 1952 (Box 78, Folder 37)
  - Brooklyn, NY, Jun 1952-Dec 1952 (Box 78, Folder 38)
  - Brooklyn, NY, Jan 1953-Jun 1953 (Box 78, Folder 39)
  - Brooklyn, NY, Jul 1953-May 1953 (Box 78, Folder 40)
  - Brooklyn, NY, 1955-1956 (Box 78, Folder 41)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 42)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1949 (Box 78, Folder 43)
  - Buffalo, NY, 1950-1952 (Box 78, Folder 44)
    Microfilm reel#: 232
  - Buffalo, NY, 1953-1956 (Box 78, Folder 45)
  - Gloversville, NY, 1949 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Kingston, NY, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Liberty, NY, 1950-1954 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Monticello, NY, 1948-1949 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - New Rochelle, NY, 1948-1952 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Port Chester, NY, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Rochester, NY, 1948-1956 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Schenectady, NY, 1948-1949 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Syracuse, NY, 1948-1956 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Utica, NY, 1948-1949 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - North Carolina: General, 1948-1953 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Ohio: General, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - Akron, OH, 1948-1956 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Cincinnati, OH, 1948-1956 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - Cleveland, OH, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Cleveland, OH, 1949 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Cleveland, OH, 1950-1951 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Cleveland, OH, 1952-1953 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    Microfilm reel#: 233
  - Cleveland, OH, 1954 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Cleveland, OH, 1955-1956 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Columbus, OH, 1949-1956 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Toledo, OH, 1948-1954 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Youngstown, OH, 1949-1953 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Oklahoma: General, 1948, 1956 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Pennsylvania: General, 1948-1956 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Allentown, PA, 1948-1949 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Erie, PA, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Harrisburg, PA, 1949-1956 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Philadelphia, PA, 1948-1949 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - Philadelphia, PA, 1950-1952 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Philadelphia, PA, 1953 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - Philadelphia, PA, 1954-1956 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1948-1950 (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1951-1953 (Box 79, Folder 34)
    Microfilm reel#: 234
  - Pittsburgh, PA, 1954-1956 (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - Reading, PA, 1949 (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - Scranton, PA, 1949 (Box 79, Folder 37)
  - Wilkes-Barre, PA, 1948-1954 (Box 79, Folder 38)
  - Rhode Island: General, 1949 (Box 79, Folder 39)
  - Providence, RI, 1948-1956 (Box 79, Folder 40)
  - Chattanooga, TN, 1948-1956 (Box 79, Folder 41)
  - Memphis, TN, 1948-1951 (Box 79, Folder 42)
  - Nashville, TN, 1949-1956 (Box 79, Folder 43)
  - Texas: General, 1954-1955 (Box 79, Folder 44)
  - Dallas, TX, 1949-1952 (Box 79, Folder 45)
  - Galveston, TX, 1948-1956 (Box 79, Folder 46)
  - Houston, TX, 1948-1956 (Box 79, Folder 47)
  - San Antonio, TX, 1952-1955 (Box 79, Folder 48)
  - Waco, TX, 1949-1956 (Box 79, Folder 49)
  - Vermont: General, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 50)
  - Virginia: General, 1950-1954 (Box 79, Folder 51)
  - Richmond, VA, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 52)
  - Seattle, WA, 1948-1956 (Box 79, Folder 53)
  - Tacoma, WA, 1953 (Box 79, Folder 54)
  - Washington, DC, 1948-1949 (Box 79, Folder 55)
  - Washington, DC, 1950-1953 (Box 79, Folder 56)
  - Washington, DC, 1954-1956 (Box 79, Folder 57)
  - West Virginia: General, 1949-1953 (Box 79, Folder 58)
  - Madison, WI, 1948-1956 (Box 79, Folder 59)
  - Milwaukee,WI, 1948-1956 (Box 79, Folder 60)
- Series III: Foreign Countries
  - Africa, 1948 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    Microfilm reel#: 235
  - Argentina, 1948 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Argentina, 1949-1950 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Argentina, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Argentina, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Argentina, 1953 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Argentina, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Argentina, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Argentina, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Australia, 1948 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - Australia, 1949 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    Microfilm reel#: 236
  - Australia, 1950 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - Australia, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Australia, 1952-1953 (Box 80, Folder 14)
  - Australia, 1954-1956 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - Austria, Jan 1948-Feb 1948 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Austria, Mar 1948-Apr 1948 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Austria, May 1948-Jun 1948 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Austria, Jul 1948-Aug 1948 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Austria, Sep 1948-Oct 1948 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    Microfilm reel#: 237
  - Austria, Nov 1948-Dec 1948 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Austria, 1949 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Austria, 1950-1952 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Austria, 1953-1956 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Belgium, Jan 1948-Jun 1948 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Belgium, Jul 1948-Dec 1948 (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - Belgium, Jan 1949-May 1949 (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - Belgium, Jun 1949-Dec 1949 (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - Belgium, 1950 (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - Belgium, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 30)